<resources>
    <string name="app_name">QlikSudoku</string>
    <string name="readme_text">Part 1.
        \n
        I agree with the author of the Programming assignment. "The assignement can grow almost indefinitely". I would like to have refactored the code in FileReader to use a utility
        class like BufferReader and also use division and modulus operators in the Solver class to
        make the code shorter and more efficient instead of the many for loops. I chose to store the
        Sudoku in a char matrix (char[][]) as a Sudoku plane basically is a matrix. To chose chars
        and not ints might seem strange but that was how I started when reading the files and I
        kept it that way in the end. All four Sudoku examples can be loaded from the menu. I did not
        implement a picker for a text file from the file system but this can be added on request.\n

        \n
        Part 2.
        \n
        I have written an algorithm that solves the Sudoku games. I tried out some variants using for
        and while loops but soon came to the conclusion that it needed to be solved by recursion. I
        spent quite some time to get the GridView to refresh for every new number that was tried by
        the algorithm so one could see the algorithm in work in the UI, but I could only manage to get
        a refresh for the full solution.
        To classify the level of the Sudoku I was thinking of calculating the blank spaces of the game.
        But I did then see that level Hard and Samurai had the same amount of blanks. But I noticed that
        the execution time for the algorithm to solve the Sudokus varied quite a lot. It is not implemented
        but I would use the amount of recursive calls needed to classify the level of the game.\n

        \n
        Part 3.
        \n
        I did not get a chance to implement part 3 I\'m afraid. I was thinking of distributing numbers
        randomly on the Sudoku board and then use the solve algorithm to know if it actually was a
        solvable Sudoku that was created.\n

        \n
        Part 4.
        \n
        If you are using the android application... well then you are looking at it (part 4) :-) .

    </string>
</resources>
